screencraft.org 2016-05-08

# Privacy Policy - ScreenCraft

#### Security

We at ScreenCraft respect your privacy and we will not sell or share your contact information with any third party without your consent. We collect information from you when you register and use our site, when you submit a screenplay for a contest, and when you purchase something.

Information that we collect may be used to make our website better. We continually endeavor to improve our sit based on the user data that we receive from you.

Information that we collect may be used to personalize your experience.

Information that we collect may be used to improve your customer service.

The email address you provide may be used to send you occasional inspiring quotes or stories, company updates, related products or services, etc. You may unsubscribe at any time.

We reserve the right to use cookies. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We may use cookies to help us understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

#### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.2013 ScreenCraft

855-503-5500  
Los Angeles, CA 90066
